<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>swopnilnep on Computer Science Society</title>
    <link>http://www.luthercss.github.io/authors/swopnilnep/</link>
    <description>Recent content in swopnilnep on Computer Science Society</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.luthercss.github.io/authors/swopnilnep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackathon Sunday April 13th</title>
      <link>http://www.luthercss.github.io/docs/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luthercss.github.io/docs/calendar/</guid>
      <description>Happy Friday!
Hackathon is happening in one week! On Saturday April 13th, the day-long event will kick-off in Olin 202 at 10AM with team formation and project brainstorming/selection. Individuals and teams will then be able to spend the day working towards creating a functioning product. Project presentations (and prizes!) will be in Olin 202 at 8PM.
A few notes: 1. It is not required for participants to stay in the room the whole day, nor spend the entire time working on the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming DS Talks</title>
      <link>http://www.luthercss.github.io/docs/ds-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luthercss.github.io/docs/ds-talks/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!
If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a bright spot amidst the April snow, check out the following lectures tomorrow and Friday, presented by Justin Marschall, a 2012 Luther Grad!
Data Science Careers for Behavioral and Social Science Majors Thursday, April 11 6:30 pm Valders 362 In an emergent, multidisciplinary field, data scientists come from diverse backgrounds. This talk highlights how one Luther 2012 psychology major pursued a career in the field of data science, while giving advice for other social science majors to do the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to CSS!</title>
      <link>http://www.luthercss.github.io/docs/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luthercss.github.io/docs/hello/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the official website of the Luther College Computer Science Society! For the 2018-2019 year, our executives are:
 Alexander Davis: President James Miller: Vice President Karina Hoff: Treasurer Swopnil N. Shrestha: Secretary  We are excited to be able to host events and workshops for the betterment of the CS community at Luther. Hope to see you at out meetings!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>